A Finding Aid to the Ad Reinhardt Papers, 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Printed Material, circa 1927-1968; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 2-4; 1.7 linear feet)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Clippings, African and Pre-Columbian Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Clippings, Architecture, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Clippings, Art History and Aesthetics, 1935, 1965-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Clippings, Artwork by Others, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, Chinese and Japanese Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2-4)
  - Clippings, Christian Art, undated; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Indian Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - Clippings, Persian Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Clippings, Various Topics, 1952, 1963-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Review, 1935, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Conference Programs, 1953-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Event Announcements, 1946-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Event Calendars, 1956-1957, 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1946-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, undated, 1940-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, circa 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1963-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Exhibition Posters, 1944-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Journals and Newsletters, 1945-1949, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Journals and Newsletters, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Listen Magazine Covers, 1940-1941, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Movie Posters (photo-reproductions), circa 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Navy Booklets, 1943-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1946, 1964-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Published Cartoons by Reinhardt, undated, circa 1936-circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Published Cartoons by Reinhardt, undated, circa 1936-circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Published Cartoons by Reinhardt, undated, circa 1936-circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Published Cartoons by Reinhardt, undated, circa 1936-circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Published Cartoons by Reinhardt, 1939-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Red and Black of Public School 88, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1938-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Conserved items from Clippings, Ad Reinhardt and Modern Art and Miscellaneous Printed Material, Archival Resource Key (Oversize 6)
    Conserved items from Box 2, Folder 44 and Box 4, Folder 8
- Scrapbooks, circa 1928-1959; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 4-5; 0.5 linear feet)
  Scrapbooks compiled by Reinhardt document his high school and college days, as well as his early career as a professional artist. Included in his scrapbook from Newtown High school and his scrapbook from his time at Columbia University are clippings of his published comic strips, covers of magazines and other school publications that he designed, as well as clippings of articles about his role in school events and awards that he won. Also found here are loose scrapbook pages spanning twenty years of his career as an artist which contain newspaper and magazine articles about Reinhardt, published cartoons, pages from exhibition catalogs, and reproductions of his artwork.
  Items are arranged chronologically.
  This series has been scanned in its entirety.
  - High School Scrapbook, circa 1928-1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Columbia Scrapbook, 1932-1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook Pages, 1939-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Artwork, circa 1946, 1950, 1961; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; (Box 4; 4 folders)
  This series contains artwork by Reinhardt including homemade Christmas cards, drawings of international architectural styles, primarily churches and temples, a sketch of a leaflet for an artist strike, and various other small sketches.
  - Christmas Cards, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Drawings of Architectural Styles, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sketch for Fine Artist Strike Leaflet, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sketches, 1950, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)